http://www.siberhegner.com/global-en/home/privacy

Privacy
Search
The following characters are not allowed : [](){}%<>\&*=
Business contacts
Find a contact person to discuss opportunities to expand your business
Corporate contacts
Find a contact person for HR, Investor and Media Relations and other corporate functions
After-sales service
Find contact details for your after-sales service requirements
Hong Kong
DKSH Hong Kong Ltd.23rd Floor, Tower A, Southmark11 Yip Hing StreetWong Chuk HangHong Kong
DKSH Hong Kong Ltd.+852 2963 6896
Monday to Friday, 8:30am-12:30pm, 2:00pm-5:30pm (HKT)
Guam
Caronel Rolex Service CenterTumon Sands Plaza, 2FTumon, Guam 96913
Frank Gradyan+1 671 649 0081frank.gradyan@dksh.com
Monday to Friday, 10am-6pm (ChST)
Guam
Caronel Watch Service CenterInside Time & Style in GPOTamuning, Guam 96913
Benito Ponce+1 671 647 2616
Monday to Thursday, Saturday, 10am-7pm (ChST)
China
DKSH (China) Ltd., 3rd Floor, Tomson Commercial Building710 Dong Fang RoadPudong, Shanghai 200122
Cassie Deng+86 21 5830 0518 1002cassie.deng@dksh.com
Monday to Friday, 9am-6pm (CST)
Singapore
DKSH South East Asia Pte Ltd625 Toa Payoh Lorong 4#03-00, Singapore 319519
DKSH South East Asia Pte Ltd+65 6222 0322
Monday to Friday, 9am-6pm (SGT)
Germany
DKSH Luxury & Lifestyle Europe GmbHStuttgarter Strasse 875179 PforzheimGermany
For repairs:+49 7231 914150For spare parts:+49 7231 914160service@mauricelacroix.de
Monday to Friday, 8am-5pm (CEST)
Click here to submit an inquiry to our after-sales services team
{{totalHits}} results
Filters
Corporate functions
Human ResourcesInvestor RelationsMediaMergers & AcquisitionsLegal
Unfortunately, no references matched your search criteria.
Overview
SourcingMarket insightsMarketing and salesDistribution and logisticsAfter-sales servicesDKSH IT backbone
DKSH commitment to privacy protection
DKSH respects your privacy and is committed to comply with applicable data protection laws and to safeguard your personal data. This Privacy Statement describes the way in which we, DKSH Management Ltd. as the data controller, and its Group companies (DKSH) collect, use and share personal data about you, how we safeguard your personal data and interact with third parties that may have access to your personal data and finally, how you can contact us in case of questions or requests.
By using this website, you consent to the collection and use of your personal data as described in this Privacy Statement. You also acknowledge that DKSH may periodically change, update or remove this Privacy Statement at its discretion. In this case, we will post updated versions of this Privacy Statement on this page. A revised Privacy Statement will apply only to data collected subsequent to its effective date. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. Your continued use of our services following the posting of changes to the Privacy Statement will mean you accept those changes.
This Privacy Statement applies to personal data collected by DKSH online, such as through this website, email and other online tools and applications, but not to offline collection.
Legal basis and personal data we collect about you
As part of your interactions with us, we may collect personal data about you as far as it is necessary to conduct our legitimate interests, to comply with a legal obligation or as agreed by you.
Most of our services do not require any form of registration, allowing you to visit our website without providing us with any information about you. However, some services may require you to register and therefore to provide us with your personal data. The types of personal data we collect depend on the interactions you have with us and the services you use, they may include your title, first name, last name, company, department, email address, phone, street, building number, zip code, city and country.
We may also collect your personal data by tracking how you interact with our website, for example by using cookies. We may collect the Internet Protocol (IP) address, a number assigned to your computer whenever you access our website to conduct system administration and report aggregated information to affiliates, business partners and/or vendors who conduct website analysis and website performance reviews on our behalf. We may further collect your utilization data, e.g. information on the beginning, end and extent of each access, and information on the telecommunications services you accessed. In some instances, we may ask for your consent for collecting and using your personal data for the purposes as outlined in this Privacy Statement, in particular for sending you marketing materials, such as explanatory brochures and information or newsletters or when you submit contact forms or participate in any online survey.
How we use your personal data
We will only collect and use personal data about you as described in this Privacy Statement and as necessary
To provide you with our services and to process your order
To respond to your requests
To manage our customer relationship with you
To send you relevant marketing materials
To invite you to register for an event
To invite you to participate in an online survey
To provide you with our media and investor relations information
To prevent fraud or other illegal activities, such as willful attacks to DKSH information technology systems
To establish or preserve a legal claim or defense or to support any legal or criminal investigation
And otherwise to the extent as permitted or required by applicable laws
We may further anonymize and aggregate data collected through this website for statistical purposes to help us improve our products and services. Subject to your specific permission that we may collect separately and to your right to request that we cease such activities at any time, we may also use your personal data to send you promotional material or newsletters that we think may be of interest to you.
We may also use data collected through this website to build a profile of your interests and show you relevant content or adverts on other sites.
Cookies and usage tracking
We use cookies, small text files that are automatically placed on your computer’s hard drive when you access certain websites and similar technologies, directly or through third parties, such as web analytics services like Google Analytics. Cookies allow us to store information, such as your domain name, your internet service provider, your operating system, the date and time of access, the pages you visit or the types of searches you perform.
Because we respect your right to privacy, you can choose not to allow some types of cookies. Click on the Cookie Settings button below to find out more about the cookie categories and to change our default settings. However, blocking some types of cookies may impact your experience of the site and the services we are able to offer.
Cookie Settings
The types of cookies we use
Links to other websites
DKSH websites contain links to other websites. Please note that any of these sites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for the privacy practices or the content of other websites but only for the websites controlled by DKSH.
Who we share your personal data with
We may share, or otherwise disclose, your personal data to our affiliated companies or other trusted business partners providing services on our behalf, such as for technical support, to evaluate the usefulness of this website, for marketing purposes or for other types of service delivery. We have contracts in place with these parties to ensure that personal data is processed based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Statement and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
We only share your personal data with the parties mentioned above and other third parties, including governmental authorities, as far as this is necessary to provide any services that you have requested or authorized by accepting the terms of this Privacy Statement, to protect your, our or others’ rights, property or safety, to maintain the security of our services or if we are required to share your personal data to comply with applicable laws, courts or other governmental regulations, or if such disclosure is otherwise necessary in support of any legal or criminal investigation or legal proceeding.
Please note that DKSH companies and subsidiaries, as well as authorities, customers and suppliers to whom we may disclose your personal data, may be located outside your country of domicile, including countries in Asia and potentially the United States of America, whose data protection laws may differ from those in the country in which you are located. In such cases, we will ensure that appropriate safeguards are in place to protect your personal data by implementing appropriate legal mechanisms, such as EU Standard Contractual Clauses. For more information about the safeguards we take, please send us an email via a form here:
Online Communications
How we secure your personal data
DKSH has implemented technical and organizational measures to protect your personal data against accidental or unlawful destruction, loss or alteration and against unauthorized disclosure or access to personal data we store. This includes training of our personnel who may have access to your personal data.
How long we store your personal data
We will store your personal data as long as required to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Statement, unless a longer or shorter retention period is required or permitted by law.
Your rights in respect to your personal data
You have the right to request to be notified about what personal data we hold from you and to request the correction or deletion of your personal data that is held by us or by a third party with whom we conduct business. In addition, where the processing of your personal data is based on your consent, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. Additionally, you may have the right to receive a copy of the Personal Data we hold concerning you. Please be aware that the withdrawal of consent shall not affect the lawfulness of processing based on your consent before its withdrawal. Under certain circumstances, you have further the right to object to or to request the restriction of the processing of your personal data and, if you reside in the EU, you may lodge a complaint to your data protection authority if you consider that the processing of your personal data infringes applicable laws.
If you would like to make such request, please contact us as described in the section “How to contact us” below. After providing proof of identity, we will respond within a reasonable time.
How to contact us
If you have any questions, comments or concerns about this Privacy Statement, or want to request access to your personal data or exercise your privacy rights, please contact us at:
DKSH Management Ltd.
Wiesenstrasse 8
8008 Zurich
Switzerland
Online Communications
This Privacy Statement is effective as of November 1, 2019.
Save page to basket
Print
About us
Discover why we are the trusted partner for companies looking to grow their business in Asia and beyond.
Market Expansion Services
Sustainability
Careers
As a services company, people are our greatest asset. Take your next career step with us.
Career opportunities
Investors
View and download DKSH shareholder information and stock prices.
Share information
Media
Access our latest news, publications, events and success stories.
Read our latest news
Delivering growth – in Asia and beyond.
© DKSH Management Ltd.
Terms and conditions
Privacy
Imprint
Delivering growth – in Asia and beyond.
© DKSH Management Ltd.
Close
Cancel
You are now leaving our website. Please click "proceed" or "cancel" if you wish to remain on this website.
